<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wict</string>
    <string name="title_about">Info</string>
    <string name="fragment_title_about">WICT Tech It Out</string>
    <string name="title_schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="title_location">Location</string>
    <string name="title_sponsor">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="title_bios">Bios</string>

    <!-- Action Menu strings -->
    <string name="am_register_title">Register</string>


    <!-- Fragment text -->
    <string name="about_wict_text">Almost half of American adults are using digital voice assistants on their smartphones, in their cars and on other devices such as Amazon Echo and Google Home. The advances in recent years of technologies to support voice and conversational user interfaces are transporting our businesses and society into a new age of voice control.
&lt;br /&gt;Join us at WICT TIO 2018 and meet some of the experts who will demo products and talk about how voice and conversational user interfaces are designed, what technologies enable them, how they are being used, and why they are changing our lives.
&lt;br /&gt;Our event is open to the public, including men and women. Students under 18 must be supervised by an adult.
&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER TODAY!
http://www.wictphiladelphia.org/event/tio2018 </string>

    <string name="special_thanks">Very special thanks to these amazing members of WICT of Greater Philadelphia who contributed their many talents,
        and devoted countless hours of their time to help create and organize
        WICT Tech It Out 2018: Allison Sims, Brenda Belkin, Chelsea Badeau, Chelsey May, Eileen Murphy, Emily Nikoo, Erin Kelly, Jeanne Ciampa,
        Jill Formichella, Laila Imam, Lauren Blevins, Manasa Kashi, Marichelle Rocha, Melissa Doogan, Nancy Rieti,
        Nidhi Desai, Stephanie Higgins. And thanks to TechWomen Philly.
        \n\nIn this Age of Voice Control--print is still important.
        The Greater Philadelphia Chapter of WICT would like to recognize our amazing in-kind designer Signature
        for the beautiful branding and design work in support of Tech It Out 2018.</string>

    <string name="location_invite">Join us for WICT Philadelphia Tech It Out event at: </string>
    <string name="location">Villanova University, 800 E Lancaster Avenue, Villanova, PA, 19085</string>

    <string name="registration_url">https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/eventReg?oeidk=a07ef910bkua2d2fc1c</string>
</resources>
